VUYANI LUDWABA

22 Ntshekisa Road

New Brighton

Port Elizabeth

6200

vee.dwaba@gmail.com

0615158308

A Dedicated and a performance driven professional with experience in Customer service, consulting, Administration, Merchandising and Warehousing.

A Specialist in Sales, Customer care, Negotiating, SEO Content writing, Digital Marketing and Google ads.

I am able to communicate well with people at all levels. I excel at using my own initiative and am flexible in my approach to work duties. I have superb interpersonal, logical and reasoning skills, strong communication skills and problem-solving abilities.

In addition to possessing excellent verbal and written communication skills, I possess a strong attention to detail and a proactive mindset, enabling me to identify potential issues and provide proactive solutions. I thrive in fast-paced environments, and I am comfortable multitasking and managing competing priorities while maintaining a high level of professionalism.

I am Multilingual, speak five languages, possess a vast amount of knowledge and skills that is spread across different industries.

----- WORK EXPERIENCE

Dataforce by Transperfect

Freelancer

January 2024 -

Part time freelancer for remote work

Volkswagen(Quest Staffing)

CIC specialist

November 2022 – April 2023

Cic direct specialist

National Debt Review Centre

Debt consultant

March 2022 - July 2022

Debt review consulting.

Upskilled to debt removal.

WNS Global Services - Port Elizabeth, Eastern

Cape

Call centre representative

October 2019 - April 2021

Telkom Fibre sales department

Red cross campaign

OTS directory services

Upskilled to Billing department

DHL - Johannesburg, Gauteng

Picker/Packer, Warehouse Storeman,

Supervisor

September 2016 - Nov 2017

Picker

		_		_	_		_
⋖.	r	റ	r	Δ	n	าล	n

Promoted to team leader

Promoted to supervisor



EDUCATION

High school or equivalent

United Church School – Matric (Johannesburg, Gauteng) **2009**

Midrand graduate institute - Marketing (Johannesburg, Gauteng) **2010-2011**

<u>IMM GSM Graduate School of Marketing</u> – Marketing Management (Port Elizabeth) **2012-2014**

<u>Programming Hub</u> – Digital Marketing, SEO optimization, Python, Google ads, Cyber security **2023** -



SKILLS

Customer Service (6 years), Google ads(1 year), Call centre (5 years), CSR (1 year), Microsoft Office (10+ years), Leadership(2 years), Sales (4 years), Social Media Marketing (1 year), SEO Content (1 Year) Logistics (2 years), Digital Marketing (1 year) Business development executive(6 months), Consultant(2 years)



CERTIFICATIONS AND LICENSES

Matric Certificate

Completed 2009

Digital Marketing Certificate

Completed 2024

SEO Certificate

Completed 2024



----- ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

References

References will be provided upon request